Guide to the George McTurnan Kahin papers, [ca. 1945-2000]
Kahin, George McTurnan papers, [ca. 1945-2000]
- Additions
  - James Nach- Vietnamization (Box 34, Folder 35)
  - An NBC News White Paper - Vietnam Hindsight, Dec 1971 (Box 34, Folder 36)
  - Takashi Oka, 1966 (Box 34, Folder 37)
  - S.E.Pelz- America goes to War in Vietnam; J.F. Kennedy's Decision in 1961 (Box 34, Folder 38)
  - Interviews (Box 34, Folder 39)
  - Dean Rusk (Box 34, Folder 40)
  - Items Discussed between Vice-President Johnson & President Diem (Box 34, Folder 41)
  - Pelz- 1963 (Box 34, Folder 42)
  - The Clockwork Vitenam Psychology of Pacification- J.P. Vann (Box 34, Folder 43)
  - John Steinbeck, 1966 (Box 34, Folder 44)
  - War experiences- Recapitulation (Box 34, Folder 45)
  - Books (Box 34, Folder 46)
  - D.G. Marr- World War II & the Vietnamese Revolution (Box 34, Folder 47)
  - G. McGovern, J.P. RocheDeclassified & Public Records for the Study of the Vietnam War, June 1972 (Box 34, Folder 48)
  - Sn. Mike Mansfield, Calabb Boggs,Caliborne Pell, B.A. Smith- Vietnam & South-east Asia, 1963 (Box 34, Folder 49)
  - G. Lewy- Vietnam: The Defense's Case, Dec 1978 (Box 34, Folder 50)
  - Ed Lansdale- The Cao Dai, May 1968 (Box 34, Folder 51)
  - J.A.N.Henchy- Declassified & Public Records for the Study of the Vietnam War, Mar 1988 (Box 34, Folder 52)
  - Ngo Vinh Long- Communal Property & Peasant Revolutionary Struggles in Vietnam, 1990 (Box 34, Folder 53)
  - The Journal of Strategic Studies, Dec 1981 (Box 34, Folder 54)
  - Indo-China Chronology, Jan- Mar 1966 (Box 34, Folder 55)
  - Indo-China Chronology, Oct- Dec 1996 (Box 34, Folder 56)
  - An NBC News White Paper, Vietnam Hindsight- Part II, Death of Diem (Box 34, Folder 57)
  - L. Freedman- Vietnam & the Disillusioned Strategist (Box 34, Folder 58)
  - McNamara (Box 34, Folder 59)
  - F.H. Craighill, C.R. Zelnick-Vietnam: from Elections to Negotiations & Beyond (Box 34, Folder 60)
  - Pentagon Papers- Newspaper Commentary (Box 34, Folder 61)
  - Senator McGovern's Speech of 1972 (Box 34, Folder 62)
  - The National Liberation Front- Seven Point Proposal (Box 34, Folder 63)
  - Aggression from the North Record of North Vietnam's Campaign to Conquer South Vietnam (Box 34, Folder 64)
  - Discussion with Gen. Pham Xuan Chieu- Sec. Gen. of National Leadership Council (Box 34, Folder 65)
  - Westmoreland- Speech to the National Press Club (Box 34, Folder 66)
  - Johnson- "I won't run speech." (Box 34, Folder 67)
  - Cambodia- the Administration's Version & the Historical Record (Box 34, Folder 68)
  - Deaprtment of State- A Threat to Peace- North Vietnam's Effort to Conquer South Vietnam (Box 34, Folder 69)
  - The U.S. Commitment in Vietnam: Fundamental Issues- Sec. Rusk, Gen Taylor (Box 34, Folder 70)
  - Westmoreland & Bunker- Meet the Press (Box 34, Folder 71)
  - Department of State- Aggression from the North (Box 34, Folder 72)
  - Porter Gareth:-Vietnam: The Definitive Documentation of Human Decisions, Volume 1, 1979 (Box 35)
  - Porter Gareth:-Vietnam: The Definitive Documentation of Human Decisions, Volume 2 (Box 35)
  - Snepp Frank- Decent Interval:An Insider's Account of Saigon's Indecent End Told by CIA's Chief Strategy Anaylist in Vietnam, 1977 (Box 35)
  - Ennis Thomas E.- French Policy and Developments in IndoChina, 1936 (Box 35)
  - Khanh Huynh Kim- Vietnamese Communism 1925-1945, 1982 (Box 35)
  - Porter Gareth- Vietnam- A History in Documents, 1979 (Box 35)
  - Race Jeffrey- War Comes to Long An, 1972 (Box 35)
  - Prados John- The Hidden History of the Vietnam War, 1995 (Box 35)
  - Hiebert Murray- Vietnam Notebook, 1993 (Box 35)
  - Sheehan Neil, Smith Hedrick, Kenworthy E.W., Butterfield Fox- The Pentagon Papers, July 1971 (Box 35)
  - Muti B.S.N.- Vietnam Divided: The Unfinished Struggle, 1964 (Box 35)
  - Chen King C.- Vietnam and China 1938-1954, 1969 (Box 35)
  - Kahin George Mcturnan, Lewis John W.- The United States in Vietnam: An Analysis in Depth of the History of America's Involvement in Vietnam, 1967,1969 (Box 35)
  - Van Tran Van- Our Endless War Inside Vietnam, 1978 (Box 35)
  - Nach James- The Coup D'Etat of November 1 1963, 1980 (Box 35)
  - United Staes- Vietnam Relations, 1945-1967, Books 1-12 (Box 36)
  - Footnotes to the GPO Edition of the Pentagon Papers (Box 36)
  - Thies Wallas J.- When Governments Collide, 1980 (Box 37)
  - Shaplen Robert- The Lost Revolution, 1955 (Box 37)
  - Rotter Andrew J.- The Path to Vietnam, Origins of the American Commitment to Southeast Asia, 1987 (Box 37)
  - Scigliano Robert- Sotuh Vietnam: Nation under Stress, 1963 (Box 37)
  - Herring George C.- America's Longest War: The United States and Vietnam, 1979 (Box 37)
  - Stavins Ralph, Barnet Richard J., Raskin Marcus G.- Washington Plans am Aggressive War, Aug 1971 (Box 37)
  - Raskin Marcus G., Fall Bernard B.-The Vietnam Reader- Articles & Documents on Americaan Foreign Policy & the Vietnam Crisis, Nov 1965 (Box 37)
  - Schurmann Franz, Scott Peter Dale, Zelnick Reginald- The Politics of Escalation in Vietnam, 1966 (Box 37)
  - Steinberg Blema S.- Shame & Humiliation: Presidential Decision Making on Vietnam (Box 37)
  - Porter Gareth D.- The Myth of Bloodbath: North Vietnam's Land Reform Reconsidered, Sept 1972 (Box 37)
  - Memoirs of Lt Gen Tran Van Don Serilaized in the Newspaper Dien Tin (Box 37)
  - Walter La Feber- Roosevelt, Curchill & Indochina 1942-45, dEC 1975 (Box 37)
  - Asian Survey- May 1970- Origins of the Second Indo-China War (Box 37)
  - Exploratory Talks, 1990-1991 (Box 78, Folder 4-9)
- Series VI. Lectures
  - Government 417 (omitted 1952, 1953), 1951 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - 377 Exams, 1963-64 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Exams, 1960 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Government-417 Final Exam, 1960 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Class List, 1964 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Government-377, 577/644, 1964-65 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Government 417-Exams, 1951-57 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Government 344-Class List, 1964 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Government 344-Reading Assignments, 1964 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Government 344-Class Questions, 1964 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - 344-Master-Reading List, 1964 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Government 344-Exams, 1964 (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - 344-John Provinso, 1964 (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Government 344, 1964 (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - Government 344, 1962 (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - 344-Exams, 1962 (Box 56, Folder 16)
  - 344 Papers, 1961-64 (Box 56, Folder 17)
  - Bibliography, 1962 (Box 56, Folder 18)
  - Readings-Dan Lev, 1963 (Box 56, Folder 19)
  - 344 Extra Reading Lists, 1964 (Box 56, Folder 20)
  - Indonesia 314, 1959 (Box 56, Folder 21)
  - A/S 602 Vietnam Spring, 1964 (Box 56, Folder 22)
  - F/S 601 Indonesia, 1963 (Box 56, Folder 23)
  - Government 344 Lecture Material, n.d. (Box 56, Folder 24)
  - America & S.E.A., 1945-51 (Box 56, Folder 25)
  - U.S. & Asia Book, General, U.S.-Indonesia, 1961 (Box 56, Folder 26)
  - U.S. & S.E.A. Introduction, n.d. (Box 56, Folder 27)
  - Travel, 1956 (Box 56, Folder 28)
  - Travel: S.F., 1975 (Box 56, Folder 29)
  - Travel, 1974-75 (Box 56, Folder 30)
  - Vietnamese Nationalism: Fall 1882, 1982 (Box 56, Folder 31)
  - Lectures 601/652, n.d. (Box 56, Folder 32)
  - 601/652 Papers, 1982 (Box 56, Folder 33)
  - A/S-601/Government-652: Library Reserve Room 406, 1979 (Box 56, Folder 34)
  - Students: Vietnamese Nationalism, 1982 (Box 56, Folder 35)
  - China # 1, 1983 (Box 56, Folder 36)
  - Natsir, 1937-57 (Box 56, Folder 37)
  - Mohammad Natsir-Speeches and Articles Translated by A. Brotherton, 1956 (Box 56, Folder 38)
  - Excerpts from "Capita Selecta II" M. Natsir, Translated by A. Brotherton, 1952-58 (Box 56, Folder 39)
  - Excerpts from "Capita Selecta II" Original-Indonesian Language (Box 56, Folder 40)
  - Excerpts from "Capita Selecta II" M. Natsir, Translated by A. Brotherton (and copies), 1951-54 (Box 56, Folder 41)
  - Capita Selecta II-Brotherton pg. 1-179, 1950-55 (Box 56, Folder 42)
  - Capita Selecta II-Brotherton pg. 186-, 1951-54 (Box 56, Folder 43)
  - Duplicates, 1957-59 (Box 56, Folder 44)
  - Islam, 1939-56 (Box 56, Folder 45)
  - Sjafruddin Prawiranegara-Islam "ISlam as a Compromise Between Communism and Capitalism," Mimbar Agama 10/50, 1950 (Box 56, Folder 46)
  - Islam, 1953-54 (Box 56, Folder 47)
  - Graduate Committees, 1960-65 (Box 56, Folder 48)
  - Andrea Wilcox-Sukarno Bibliography (Box 56, Folder 49)
  - Reading Materials for SEAP and FES Courses (Box 56, Folder 50)
  - Doctoral Exams, 1957-66 (Box 56, Folder 51)
  - Reading Materials on hand-Government 417, 314; FES 601, 1952-55 (Box 56, Folder 52)
  - Government 396, 1958 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Government 395, 1959 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Government 395, 1957 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - 1960, 1959-60 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - New 395, 1960 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Government 577, 1964-65 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Government 577-644, 1964-65 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - CMIP Copies, 1965 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - CMIP material, 1945-1959 (Box 76, Folder 24)
  - Government 577/644 Seminar Papers, 1965 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Government 577 Fall 1963 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Duplicates, 1948-60 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Japan I, 1945-83 (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Korea I: February 28, 1986 (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Burma, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - China & Russia: The Shaping of Chinese Attitudes (Cold Version), n.d. (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - Laos Lectures, 1962-65 (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - Laos I & II & V.N. (4+), 1971 (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - March 29-Laos and Cambodia, 1988 (Box 57, Folder 18)
  - Laos-Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 19)
  - Government 377 #2: January 24, 1973 (Box 57, Folder 20)
  - #3-January 29, 1973 (Box 57, Folder 21)
  - Vietnam Ia-Ethno-Linguistics, 1974-82 (Box 57, Folder 22)
  - Truman & S.E.A. II, 1970-94 (Box 57, Folder 23)
  - Tufts: Lectures, 1988 (Box 57, Folder 24)
  - ISIS (Kualz Lumpur) January 28, 1991-Phil. (Box 57, Folder 25)
  - Monash University: Dec. 1992 (Box 57, Folder 26)
  - John Cady-Ohio University, 1988 (Box 57, Folder 27)
  - John Cady, 1988 (Box 57, Folder 28)
  - Hanoi Conference Paper and Supplementary Material, 1971-92 (Box 57, Folder 29)
  - Hanoi-History, 1988-92 (Box 57, Folder 30)
  - Hanoi: November 24-29, Paper, 1988 (Box 57, Folder 31)
  - Tufts Conference-Feb. 26-27 1988 (Box 57, Folder 32)
  - Oregon, 1988 (Box 57, Folder 33)
  - Oregon: Sept. 29-30, 1988 (Box 57, Folder 34)
  - Tel Aviv Conference-Putative, 1989 (Box 57, Folder 35)
  - Origins of American Inolvement, 1989-90 (Box 57, Folder 36)
  - CANADA Conference: Origins of American Involvement in Vietnam, 1988-89 (Box 57, Folder 37)
  - SEASI July 13-14, 1990 (Box 57, Folder 38)
  - SEAC: Comments on D. Emmerson's "International Studies and Southeast Asianists" July 19, 1990 (Draft) (Box 57, Folder 39)
  - SOAS-June 19, 1992 (Box 57, Folder 40)
  - SOAS: Philippines, 1992 (Box 57, Folder 41)
  - Monash Paper Dec. 18, 1992 (Box 57, Folder 42)
  - Michigan (Ann Arbox) Oct. 14, 1994 (Box 57, Folder 43)
  - Book Launching: LIPI July 12, 1995 (Box 57, Folder 44)
  - FES 208: 1996 Drafts (Box 57, Folder 45)
  - YPO Card & Int'l Security, 1985 (Box 57, Folder 46)
  - Strategic & Secuity Issue-Bangkok University, 1985 (Box 57, Folder 47)
  - YPO Courses & Bio, 1984-85 (Box 57, Folder 48)
  - YPO: Travel, 1985 (Box 57, Folder 49)
  - Lecture YPO/Nationalism & Rev. in SEA, 1985 (Box 57, Folder 50)
  - Research Club, 1953 (Box 57, Folder 51)
  - Covert Level-April 4, 1996 (640 Stewart) (Box 57, Folder 52)
  - SSRC, 1983-88 (Box 57, Folder 53)
  - SSRC, 1988-91 (Box 57, Folder 54)
  - Truman Encyclopedia, 1988 (Box 57, Folder 55)
  - Intelligence Center for Develop. Policy, 1988 (Box 57, Folder 56)
  - Indonesia 1948-49: Jakarta 5/91 American Cultural Center, 1991 (Box 57, Folder 57)
  - Origins of the American Involvement March 16, 1989 in Vietnam (Box 57, Folder 58)
  - May 5, 1988: Southeast Asia Program (Box 57, Folder 59)
  - Little-Chronicled Aspects of America's Early Involvement in Vietnam-Singapore July 10, 1985 (Box 57, Folder 60)
  - Bandung in Retrospect-Singapore, 1985 (Box 57, Folder 61)
  - WBEN-Buffalo-Sept. 10, 1986 (Box 57, Folder 62)
  - Residua, 1971 (Box 57, Folder 63)
  - Santa Barbara Talk, 1972 (Box 57, Folder 64)
  - Residua: Monash, 1971 (Box 57, Folder 65)
  - Truman's SEA, 1977 (Box 57, Folder 66)
  - Tel Aviv Conference-Dec. 1989, 1988 (Box 57, Folder 67)
- Series VII. Administration
  - Cornell
    - Past Students I, 1952-1964 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Past Students II, 1954-69 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Past Student's III, 1953-64 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Government PhD Requirements, 1988 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Government Department Fellowships & T.A., 1987-88 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Comparative Government Exam, 1975 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Comparative Government, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Comp. Government-Old Exams, 1956-70 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - SE Asian Studies, 1970 (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Comp. Government Search, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - Assistantships: Government, 1974 (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - Honors, 1973 (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - Government Department: Self Study, 1974 (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - Graduate Applications, 1967-68 (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - Graduate Committees, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - Old Exams: I.R., 1968-81 (Box 45, Folder 16)
    - Absence from Campus, 1981 (Box 45, Folder 17)
    - Applicants/Admissions, 1980-81 (Box 45, Folder 18)
    - Graduate Program, 1968-75 (Box 45, Folder 19)
    - Comp. Government-Committee, 1968-79 (Box 45, Folder 20)
    - Government Department: New Appointments, 1980-81 (Box 45, Folder 21)
    - Cornell in Washington, 1982 (Box 45, Folder 22)
    - Retirement, 1980-87 (Box 45, Folder 23)
    - Cornell: Pay Roll, 1985-88 (Box 45, Folder 24)
    - Emeritus, 1988 (Box 45, Folder 25)
    - TIAA Retirement, 1987 (Box 45, Folder 26)
    - Professional Expenses for IRS, 1988 (Box 45, Folder 27)
    - Checks for Publications & Xeroxing, 1986-87 (Box 45, Folder 28)
    - IRS, 1988 (Box 45, Folder 29)
    - Reimbursements for June 14, 1984-March 31, 1986, 1984-1986 (Box 45, Folder 30)
    - Leave: Fall 1981, Courses Spring:1982, 1981-1982 (Box 45, Folder 31)
    - Released Time, 1964 (Box 45, Folder 32)
    - Finances SEA, 1986 (Box 45, Folder 33)
    - Xeroxing & Prof. Photography, 1984-86 (Box 45, Folder 34)
    - G.M.T.K.-Expenditures other than travel, 1986-87 (Box 45, Folder 35)
    - Reimbursed as of Sept. 4, 1987, 1987 (Box 45, Folder 36)
    - Travel, 1984-86 (Box 45, Folder 37)
    - Books & Journals, 1984-86 (Box 45, Folder 38)
    - Telephone & Postage Reimbursement, 1985-86 (Box 45, Folder 39)
    - G.McT. Kahin A704101 Travel, 1986-87 (Box 45, Folder 40)
    - Backup Data for period ending in August 1, 1987, 1986-87 (Box 45, Folder 41)
    - SEAP Support 1980, 1980 (Box 45, Folder 42)
    - Application to the Christpoher Reynolds Foundation, 1979-80 (Box 45, Folder 43)
    - Fellowship (Externally Funded), 1990-91 (Box 45, Folder 44)
    - (G.K.) SEAP: Expenditures, 1975-76 (Box 45, Folder 45)
    - Research Finances, 1964-71 (Box 45, Folder 46)
    - NY: Carnegie, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 47)
    - Kahin-Golay Luce Proposal, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 48)
    - Visitors I, 1977-89 (Box 45, Folder 49)
    - Visitors II, 1980-82 (Box 45, Folder 50)
    - Thursday Luncheon, 1979 (Box 45, Folder 51)
    - Parking, 1983-87 (Box 45, Folder 52)
    - ASEAN Visit: April 4-6, 1982, 1982 (Box 45, Folder 53)
    - Japan & SEA Addresses, 1967 (Box 45, Folder 54)
    - Addresses, 1975 (Box 45, Folder 55)
    - Thailand: Addresses, 1979 (Box 45, Folder 56)
    - N.Y.T.-"Loss of Saigon", 1975 (Box 45, Folder 57)
    - Weaponry, 1974 (Box 45, Folder 58)
    - Ideas & Data: Unfiled, 1971 (Box 45, Folder 59)
    - U.S. Policy: U.S. Ideas, 1973 (Box 45, Folder 60)
    - New Material: Lectures, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 61)
    - G.K. Ideas, 1970 (Box 45, Folder 62)
    - L.B.J., 1964-72 (Box 45, Folder 63)
    - Dialogue Discussion Paper, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 64)
    - Truman & SEA, 1972-73 (Box 45, Folder 65)
    - Truman & SEA, 1952 (Box 45, Folder 66)
    - Eisenhower & SEA, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 67)
    - Eisenhower & SEA Feb. 16, 1973, 1973 (Box 45, Folder 68)
    - Imprint of J.F. Dulles on SEA, 1966-74 (Box 45, Folder 69)
    - U.S.-Interventions in SEA Book, Ideas, 1972-78 (Box 45, Folder 70)
    - Book Outline, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 71)
    - Book: U.S & SEA, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 72)
    - Further Expansion of Kyoto Paper, 1949-72 (Box 45, Folder 73)
    - Human Rights Internships, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 74)
  - General Administration & Research
    - N.E.H. Grant Application, 1981-2 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Application-Duplicate, 1980-81 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - N.E.H. Rejection, 1980-81 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - N.E.H. Application: March 25, 1980, 1980-81 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - N.E.H. Reports Due by June 30th, 1979-82 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Report of March 7, 1983 on Cornell's Contribution, 1983 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - N.E.H.-Not Yet Reimbursed, 1982-83 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - N.E.H.-Close Out by June 15, 1983, 1983 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - N.E.H.-Revised Budget May 27, 1981, 1980-81 (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Indirect Costs (72% of salaries exclusive of benefits), 1980-81 (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - Nadina Gardener, 1980-81 (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - Copy for Stan O'Connor (NEH Proposal), 1981-82 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Budgets: New N.E.H., 1981-83 (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - N.E.H.-Re-application, 1981 (Box 46, Folder 14)
    - N.E.H. Proposal, 1980 (Box 46, Folder 15)
    - Guggenheim, 1975-86 (Box 46, Folder 16)
    - Guggenheim Accounts/Duplicate & Proposal, 1975-76 (Box 46, Folder 17)
    - Petition AAS, 1973 (Box 46, Folder 18)
    - Political Prisoners Issue, 1971-74 (Box 46, Folder 19)
    - General Correspondence, 1972-74 (Box 46, Folder 20)
    - CCAS-Boston, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 21)
    - C.C.A.S., 1973-74 (Box 46, Folder 22)
    - Additional Data for Addition, 1978-1981 (Box 46, Folder 23)
    - March 3rd Draft & Correspondence, 1978 (Box 46, Folder 24)
    - Human Rights: New Data Fall 1978, Winter 1978-9, 1978 (Box 46, Folder 225)
    - Human Rights, 1978-80 (Box 46, Folder 26)
    - H.R.-Old Drafts (with some unused material), n.d. (Box 46, Folder 27)
    - Far Eastern Studies, 1952-58 (Box 46, Folder 28)
    - 601 Malaya, 1956-61 (Box 46, Folder 29)
    - F.E.S. 601, 1961 (Box 46, Folder 30)
    - Goat 342: Lectures, 1990 (Box 46, Folder 31)
    - Khanh: The Vietnam War, 1990 (Box 46, Folder 32)
    - Travel, 1965 (Box 46, Folder 33)
    - Indonesia-Finances, 1987 (Box 46, Folder 34)
    - Travel, 1970 (Box 46, Folder 35)
    - Travel Documents, 1970 (Box 46, Folder 36)
    - Travel, 1972-73 (Box 46, Folder 37)
    - Research Assistance, 1969 (Box 46, Folder 38)
    - 687 Bibliog: 1988 (xeroxes), 1988 (Box 46, Folder 39)
    - Master File-Syllabus, 1988 (Box 46, Folder 39)
    - Syllabus: 687, 1988 (Box 46, Folder 40)
    - 687: Essays, 1988 (Box 46, Folder 41)
    - Research Bibliog: Goat 687, 1988 (Box 46, Folder 42)
    - Library, 1988 (Box 46, Folder 43)
    - 687 Term Papers, 1988 (Box 46, Folder 44)
    - Quiz: 687, 1988 (Box 46, Folder 45)
    - Essay Questions & Grades, 1988 (Box 46, Folder 46)
    - Students: 687, 1988 (Box 46, Folder 47)
    - Government 687, 1987 (Box 46, Folder 48)
    - Short Papers 687, 1986 (Box 46, Folder 49)
    - 687-Budgets & Incompletes, 1986 (Box 46, Folder 50)
    - 687, 1986 (Box 46, Folder 51)
    - 687:Research, 1980-86 (Box 46, Folder 52)
    - Government 687: Prognosis, 1986 (Box 46, Folder 53)
    - 687: Students, 1986 (Box 46, Folder 54)
    - Judith Reppy Reports, 1986-87 (Box 46, Folder 55)
    - Lectures & Readings: 687, 1986 (Box 46, Folder 56)
    - Students-687, 1987 (Box 46, Folder 57)
    - Coalition for a New Foreign Policy, 1980-82 (Box 46, Folder 58)
    - Congressional Voting Record, 1980 (Box 46, Folder 59)
    - Afghanistan/Pakistan, 1980-85 (Box 46, Folder 60)
    - "Angola and the CIA", 1980 (Box 46, Folder 61)
    - Vance on Brzezinski, 1980 (Box 46, Folder 62)
    - Cuba, 1979 (Box 46, Folder 63)
    - Frank Church-3rd World Revolution, 1984 (Box 46, Folder 64)
    - Haig: Senate Hearing, 1981 (Box 46, Folder 65)
    - "Left"-Center-"Right", 1980 (Box 46, Folder 66)
    - Kissinger I, 1979 (Box 46, Folder 67)
    - Kissinger II, 1970 (Box 46, Folder 68)
    - War Powers Act Violation, 1980 (Box 46, Folder 69)
    - April-May 1980, 1980 (Box 46, Folder 70)
    - Iran, 1979-81 (Box 46, Folder 71)
    - April 14, 1986, 1986 (Box 46, Folder 72)
    - Lebanon, 1958-59 (Box 46, Folder 73)
    - ASEAN: Cambodia, 1981-82 (Box 46, Folder 74)
    - Refugees, 1979 (Box 46, Folder 75)
    - Nicaragua, 1982-1983 (Box 46, Folder 76)
    - Nicaragua: Covert, 1983-84 (Box 46, Folder 77)
    - KAL 007, 1983 (Box 46, Folder 78)
    - OPIC, 1977-78 (Box 46, Folder 79)
    - International Relations of East Asia, 1967 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Donald Luce Correspondence, 1967 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Oau Troung Thanh Correspondence, 1963 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - David Schoenbrun Correspondence, 1967 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - IREA, 1968-69 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - New Funds, 1968 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - David Mozingo Correspondence, 1969 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Santa Barbara, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - The Evening Sun: "Lattimiore Denies Being Spy", 1950 (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Statement of Lattimore, 1950 (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Indonesian Roundtable, 1968 (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - Indonesia: Economic, 1968 (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - SEADAG, 1968-69 (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - Andrew Nathan Correspondence, 1969-70 (Box 47, Folder 14)
    - Government Dept. Reuniting, 1968-69 (Box 47, Folder 15)
    - China, 1967-70 (Box 47, Folder 16)
    - Center for Strategic Studies, Washington D.C. May 20-21, 1968, 1968 (Box 47, Folder 17)
    - Richard M. Pfeffer Correspondence, 1968 (Box 47, Folder 18)
    - State Deptartment, 1968 (Box 47, Folder 19)
    - Tokyo, 1969 (Box 47, Folder 20)
    - Brookings, 1969 (Box 47, Folder 21)
    - International Relations of East Asia Project, 1966 (Box 47, Folder 22)
    - SEA-DAG, 1966 (Box 47, Folder 23)
    - Cornell, 1969 (Box 47, Folder 24)
    - Chairman: Grad-Com's, 1966-67 (Box 47, Folder 25)
    - Grad. Students in field, 1970-71 (Box 47, Folder 26)
    - Kian Chee Goh, 1969 (Box 47, Folder 27)
    - Grad. Students-Government, 1967-1969 (Box 47, Folder 28)
    - General, 1983 (Box 47, Folder 29)
    - Grad. Students, 1968-69 (Box 47, Folder 30)
    - Courses & Seminars/Government, 1968-69 (Box 47, Folder 31)
    - Government Graduate Regulations, 1969 (Box 47, Folder 32)
    - Government-Grad. Applicants & Fellowships, 1963-70 (Box 47, Folder 33)
    - SEAP-Fellowship Applicants, 1968-73 (Box 47, Folder 34)
    - Fellowship Policy, 1969 (Box 47, Folder 35)
    - Fulbright-Hays, 1969 (Box 47, Folder 36)
    - Fall 1972, 1972 (Box 47, Folder 37)
    - Government: Current, 1970-72 (Box 47, Folder 38)
    - Fulbright, 1960-62 (Box 47, Folder 39)
    - Research in SE Asia by Others, 1972-1973 (Box 47, Folder 40)
    - Research Fellowships, 1967-70 (Box 47, Folder 41)
    - Whyte's on the Process of Political Persuasion, n.d. (Box 47, Folder 42)
    - Library I, 1964-69 (Box 47, Folder 43)
    - Library II, 1967-68 (Box 47, Folder 44)
    - David Kaser, 1968-69 (Box 47, Folder 45)
    - SEAP-Faculty Research Plans, 1968-72 (Box 47, Folder 46)
    - Dec. 12-Ford, 1967 (Box 47, Folder 47)
    - SEAP Data, 1968-69 (Box 47, Folder 48)
    - Ford Grant(10 Year) SEAP, 1963-68 (Box 47, Folder 49)
    - SEAP-Budget Future, 1962-72 (Box 47, Folder 50)
    - SEAP-Financial Data, 1969-70 (Box 47, Folder 51)
    - Rockefeller Consultanship I, 1963-65 (Box 47, Folder 52)
    - Pol Sei Association, 1964 (Box 47, Folder 53)
    - Los Banos-Cornell, 1964-65 (Box 47, Folder 54)
    - Anthropology, n.d. (Box 47, Folder 55)
    - Trip, 1962-65 (Box 47, Folder 56)
    - Rockefeller, 1965 (Box 47, Folder 57)